Good afternoon, hello. I’m asking people from
Добрый день здравствуйте Я вот людей из
Russia how you feel about the
России спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
mobilization, which was announced yesterday
мобилизации которая вчера была объявлена
perfectly super And against this background, how do you feel
прекрасно супер А как на этом фоне вы
about the fact that yesterday
относитесь к тому что вчера
Azov was given to Ukraine in exchange for
Азов отдали в Украину взамен на
Medvedchuk
медведчука
Well, you know, there is a good anecdote if the wife
Ну знаете есть хороший анекдот если жена
went to a neighbor who knows who  worse
ушла к соседу неизвестно кому хуже
I just can’t understand here I am from Ukraine
Я просто не могу понять вот я из Украины
I want to understand why Russia started this
Я хочу понять почему Россия начала эту
special operation at first they said that there would be
спецоперацию сначала говорили что будет
denocification
деноцификация
yes but now those who you call
да но теперь тех кого вы называете
Nazis are giving back to Ukraine
нацистами отдаете назад в Украину
said that they were called Nazis by the
сказал что Их назвали нацистами
Nazis
нацисты
and they didn’t even let them see if
причем Даже не дали посмотрите если
ozonocysts why yesterday  they exchanged these
озоноцисты почему вчера обменяли этих
Nazis to Ukraine they gave them away and they took
нацистов в Украину отдали а забрали
Medvedchuk why
медведчука почему
I see it turns out you ruined a bunch of
я так смотрю получается вы угробили кучу
your soldiers now you send these
своих солдат теперь отдаете этих
Nazis back to Ukraine and mobilize
нацистов назад в Украину и мобилизируйте
new soldiers so that they don’t die
новых солдат чтобы снова не умирали
again Wait a minute they caught well-
не Подождите поймали хорошо
trained military Azov people
обученных военных азовцев
put them in jail So they flew by
посадили их в тюрьму Так им пролетел
Greetings from  Motherland so 50 people banged at
Привет с Родины так 50 человек грохнуло
once it's you gr  gasped then I know
сразу это вы грохнули тогда я знаю
Well, let us,
Хорошо пусть мы
but now they were happy to send them
а сейчас их с радостью отправили
to the one who sent Hello from the Motherland, what
к тому кто отправлял Привет с Родине что
will happen to them in their homeland now
теперь с ними будет на родине дальше
Let's see the stories, I
Давайте посмотрим истории расскажет я
understand, that is, it turns out, remember how the
понял то есть получается помните как
Ukrainian classic today at the
украинского классика сегодня на
Patriarchs will be a story
Патриарших будет история
once but  I don’t remember such
когда-то но не помню такого
Ukrainian
украинского
I know I don’t know how Ukrainian he is,
знаю не знаю сколько он украинский
let’s look right, I
давайте так смотрите правильно я
figured it out here
разобрался тут
I specifically gave Azov to Ukraine,
я специально отдали Азов в Украину
we don’t know who who is what But
мы не знаем кто кого чего А вот смотрите
you look like a person who supports
Вы как человек который поддерживает
mobilization when you go to the military registration and enlistment office I don’t
мобилизацию когда идете в военкомат не
go I grew up And how old are you  a little
иду я вырос А сколько Вам лет чуть
more That is, you support just
побольше То есть вы поддержите просто
to take others away, but don’t, I’m ready,
чтобы забирали других но не надо я готов
as if I have a friend, for example, I
как бы у меня друг например сам ходил
can’t walk it myself, you support mobilization
его нельзя вы поддержите мобилизацию
so that someone is sent to war in a
чтобы кого-то отправляли на войну в
foreign country, not you, it’s impossible
чужую страну не вас так вас невозможно
for us to go to war in a foreign country
чтобы мы шли воевать в чужую страну
say that you support mobilization
говорите что вы поддержите мобилизацию
for war in a foreign country in Ukraine
на войну в чужую страну в Украину
do not raise you want
не поднимаете вы хотите
it all ready for anything  x they don’t take some
это все готовы на всех не берут какая-то
garbage, well, don’t forget. Well, what about a person
фигня ну вы не забывайте Ну что человеку
who is more than 50, he’s actually In the
которому побольше 50 он вообще-то В
ninety-first I served there that I
девяносто первом служил я там что я
heard that Wagner is recruiting
слышал что Вагнер набирают Независимо
Regardless of this age, no recruiting,
так от такого возраста нет набирают вне
regardless of age, it’s important to recruit
зависимости от возраста важно набирает
people who are healthy  have the
людей которые имеют здоровье имеют
skills to do this again I say that my friend
навыки этому еще раз говорю что мой друг
Odnoklassnik being a kropovik That
Одноклассник будучи кроповиком То есть
is,
он
during his service he worked
во время своей службы он работал
Maroon beret imagine Yes,
Краповый берет представляете Да
if you are interested then you will find
если интересно потом найдете посмотрите
what the Maroon beret is That is, this is the
что такое Краповый берет То есть это
Special Forces Elite of
Элита спецназа
501 He was told
501 год Ему сказали
But you are already old young will be on
Но ты уже старый молодых будут на
lethal not young ones Well, I understand that
убойных не молодых бы Ну я понимаю что
if people served in the army after the 50th
бы если бы в армии служили люди после 50
war, they would have ended long ago,
войны бы давно кончились вот
well, because they work more with their heads
ну потому что они головой больше
than young people, well, they don’t
работают чем молодежь вот Ну вот не
take us because we are already considered sick people,
берут нас потому что мы вот больные люди
I understand that it turns out
уже считаются понял то есть получается
that  in Russia you support
что в России вы поддерживаете
mobilization, but because you
мобилизацию но из-за того что вы
think with sick people they won’t take you, they
считаете с больными людьми вас не
will take someone
возьмут возьмут кого-то другого это
else  support
поддержите
I'm still ready
я еще я готов
man unfortunately with my
человек к сожалению с моими
illnesses But it turns out that I
заболеваниями Но получается значит я
just understand for sure that they won't
просто точно понимаете что вас не
take you
возьмут
I'm ready You definitely understand that you are ready
Я готов Вы точно понимаете что вы готов
but you definitely understand that they won't take
но Вы точно понимаете что вас не возьмут
you  without this, it
Вот ты нужен вроде скажу Да без этого
doesn’t work in a shorter way, but it’s
короче не получается да вот
like, is it really that the Motherland is no longer in
типа чтобы вот уже разве Родина уже не в
danger
опасности
once it announces the mobilization of the need for people and
раз объявляет мобилизацию нужно людей и
that It’s not a danger, they are the danger
что Это же не опасность они опасность
of the NATO countries, you understand problems are coming
страны НАТО понимаете наступают проблемы
[laughter]
[смех]
Are you not just going to be shorter
Ты что не просто короче буду офигенный
it will be so
золотого меняли до это это будет как
beautiful
красиво
Ukraine
Украина
Let's say in Russian all these Russians
Давайте по-русски скажем все русские эти
saw who want to go to war Ukraine
увидели которые хотят на войну Украина
meets his soldiers as heroes as
встречает своих солдат как героев
president of inclusion he addresses them
президентом включения он к ним
personally
обращается он лично
to thank them
благодарить
in Russia That they brought somewhere there they took a
в России Что привезли где-то там
picture of the plane as they landed
сфоткали самолет как они высадились
from afar all
издалека все
A  where where they are not speeches where the president
А где где их не речи где президент
who lives there lives his hand there or
который там живет им руку там или
says that Well done
говорит что Молодцы
in Russia
в России
meat and  empire
мясо империи
Like comments and petra we are
Ставьте лайк комментует и петры мы деда
NATO's grandfather
НАТО Мы в опыте вида и подписываетесь на